瓦胡島  卡胡庫  聯邦調查局安全屋
朱莉  火奴魯魯警局護送人員來了
Julie. The HPD escort's here.
待在這  等我來找你
Stay here. Wait till I come for you.
我真的要謝謝你  弗蘭克
I really want to thank you, Frank.
我知道你跟家人很長時間不在一起
I know how long you've been away from your family,
就是為了照顧我
looking after me.
這是我的工作
It's the job.
但是聽你這么說我很欣慰
But I appreciate that.
東躲西藏
The running...
我無法再這么做了
I can't do it anymore.
今天你作證之后  就不必再東躲西藏了
After you testify today, the running stops.
你就能重新開始生活  朱莉
You're going to get a fresh start, Julie.
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
弗蘭克·摩爾  美國執法官
Frank Moore, U.S. Marshals.
很高興認識你   我是蒂姆·卡拉漢警官
It's good to meet you. I'm Officer Tim Callahan.
這位是我的搭檔  喬·李警官
This is my partner, Officer Joe Lee.
我們來護送你和證人前往法院
We're here to escort you and the witness to the courthouse.
她和我坐這輛無標識的車  你們在前面帶路
She rides with me in the unmarked. You guys are out front.
-你們有無線電嗎  -有  當然有
- You got a radio for me? - Yeah. Of course.
老天  當你們提到說偏遠地區
Man, when you guys say remote location,
還真沒有開玩笑啊
you're not kidding.
我去帶她下來
I'll go get her.
她在這里面
She's in here.
天堂執法者
第一季 第十六集
-成浩·凱利  -說
- Chin Ho Kelly? - Yo.
毫無疑問  那是
That is, without a doubt,
我這輩子吃過最好吃的東西
the greatest thing I've ever tasted in my life.
簡直是好吃到違法啊
This should be illegal, it's so good.
-那是什么  -可可泡芙
- What the hell is it? - Coco puffs.
莉莉哈面包店每天會賣出7000份呢
Liliha Bakery sells, like, 7,000 of these a day.
棒極了
It's genius.
好吃  都有什么成分  黃油  奶油
It's amazing. What is it? Butter, cream,
巧克力  再放點黃油
chocolate, a little more butter.
我一直以為我這一生最后一頓飯想吃
You know, I always thought that I wanted my last meal
我媽媽做的千層面
to be my mother's lasagna,
但是那被淘汰了  不吃千層面了
but that is out. It's out. No more.
我要吃這個  不要甜點
I want this. I want no dessert.
不要開胃菜  就給我一大盒這個就行
I want no appetizer. Just a big box of these.
不錯
Nice.
蕾切爾來電
那不是你孩子的母親嗎
Wasn't that the mother of your child?
你知道史上最棒的發明是什么嗎
You know what the greatest invention of all time is?
-什么  -手機的忽略鍵
- What? - It's the "Ignore" button.
我有個理論  不管是誰
You know, I have a theory-- whoever invented
發生了現代手機  他肯定也有前妻
the modern cellular phone also had an ex-wife.
我以為你們的關系不那么僵了
I thought you guys were doing better, though.
是啊  她畢竟和那人還是夫妻
Yeah. But she's still married to another guy.
明白嗎
You know what I mean?
只對一個人生氣  要容易一些
I mean, it's a lot easier being angry at one person.
再說  蕾切爾和我  我們有共同語言
Besides, Rachel and I, we have our own language.
互相理解
It's an understanding.
她不接我的電話  我就留言留個問題
She ducks my call. I leave a message with a question.
她打回來  我不接
She calls me back. I duck that call.
她留言回答問題
She leaves an answer.
我們就不必在格蕾絲面前爭吵了
We don't have to argue in front of Grace.
-很有效  -是啊
- It all works out. - Yeah.
科諾
Kono?
都過來  伙計們
Let's go, guys.
有任務
We got something.
-什么事  -火奴魯魯警局派了兩名警官
- S'up. - All right, HPD assigned two officers
護送一位聯邦執法官和一位重要證人
to escort a federal marshal and a high value witness
證人名叫朱莉·馬斯特
named Julie Masters.
聯邦執法官在卡胡庫的安全屋
The federal marshal's been watching her
照看她
in a safe house in Kahuku,
她是謀殺指控的關鍵證人
and she's the key witness in a murder trial
被告是這個人
against this guy,
艾倫·布萊納
Aaron Brenner.
他是巴哈販毒集團的主要經銷人
He's a major distributor for the Baja drug cartel.
沒有朱莉控方就無法立案
Now, the prosecution cannot make a case without Julie,
沒有證人的話  法官就不得不在今天
and without a witness, the judge is going to be forced
下午五點在布萊納交保后釋放他
to release Brenner on bail at 5:00 p.m. today.
這么說  販毒集團在不惜一切代價地
Okay, so the cartel's going to do everything they can
阻止這個女孩出庭
to keep this girl out of court?
是啊  他們過去十年
Absolutely. They've been trying
一直想把這個惡棍關進大牢
to lock this monster up for ten years.
朱莉的證詞可以使他入獄
And Julie's testimony can do it.
好吧  我們怎么做
All right, where do we come in?
火奴魯魯警局和兩名派去
HPD's lost contact with the two SWAT guys
護送她的特警失去了聯系
they sent in to pick her up.
無線電沒有回音
I mean, there's no comms on the radio.
深入卡胡庫的地區沒有手機信號
There's no cell service that deep in Kahuku.
那位執法官呢
What about the marshal?
他的衛星電話沒有回音
There's no comms on his sat phone.
那我們這是護送任務還是營救任務
Okay, so what are we, an escort or a rescue mission?
現在我們兩樣一起干
Right now we're both. Okay?
我們要找到她
We need to find her,
把她救出來  然后我們要
we need to secure her, and then we need
在下午五點把她送到法庭作證
to transport her to the courthouse 5:00 p.m. to testify.
明白嗎
All right?
就是不接
Bing.
我是丹尼·威廉姆斯警探
This is Detective Danny Williams.
現在不方便接電話  請留言
I'm not available. Please leave a message.
威廉姆斯警探  我是你的前妻
Detective Williams, this is your ex-wife.
我要你在周六八點來接格蕾絲  而不是九點
I need you to pick up Grace at 8:00 instead of 9:00
因為我和斯坦要去參加一個活動
on Saturday because Stan and I are going to an event.
天啊
Oh, my God!
待在那  親愛的
Stay there, sweetheart.
從車里出來
Get out of the car.
不  我不會離開我的女兒
No, I'm not leaving my daughter.
趕緊給我下車
Get out of the car now.
好了  格蕾絲  到前面來  快
Okay, Grace. Get over the seat. Get over of the seat, Grace.
爬過來  快
Climb over the seat now.
退后  退后
Get back. Get back.
你還好嗎
You okay?
威廉姆斯警探  我是你的前妻
Detective Williams, this is your ex-wife.
我要你在周六八點來接格蕾絲  而不是九點
I need you to pick up Grace at 8:00 instead of 9:00
因為我和斯坦要去參加一個活動
on Saturday because Stan and I are going to an event.
天啊
Oh, my God!
待在那  親愛的
Stay there, sweetheart.
丹尼  怎么了
Danny? What's up?
從車里出來
Get out of the car.
不  我不會離開我的女兒
No, I'm not leaving my daughter.
趕緊給我下車
Get out of the car now.
-丹尼  -蕾切爾  格蕾絲在哪
- Danny. - Rachel. Where's Grace?
她沒事
Um, she's okay.
我們的車被搶走了
We were carjacked.
他們拿著槍
Um, they had guns.
我們在警察局
We're at the police station.
待在那  待在那  用不了五分鐘我就到
Don't move. Don't move. I'll be there in five minutes.
嘿  怎么了
Hey. What? What?
格蕾絲和蕾切爾被劫車了
Grace and Rachel got carjacked.
-他們還好嗎  -我不知道
- Are they okay? - I don't know.
聽著  需要什么  就給我打電話
Listen, you need anything, you call, all right?
-不管需要什么  -好  我得走了
- Anything. - All right. I got to go.
去吧
Go, go, go, go, go.
好了  我們出發吧
All right, uh, let's go.
守住周邊  我們要進去了
Secure the perimeter. We're going in.
伙計們
Guys.
阿成  掩護我
Chin, cover me.
我找到一具尸體
I got a body.
我掩護你
I got you.
-是誰  -是執法官  死了
- Who is it? - It's the Marshal. He's gone.
科諾  上
Kono. Go.
安全
Clear.
好的  我們要找的是兩個人  塊頭比較大
All right. We're looking for two guys, both big.
11碼鞋  沒有強行闖入的痕跡
Size 11. There's no forced entry,
就是說執法官為他們留了門
which means the Marshal left the door open for them.
他沒想到他們是壞人
He didn't think they were a threat.
是因為他們穿著火奴魯魯警員的制服
It's cause they were wearing HPD uniforms.
查查車子
Check the car.
安全
Clear.
兩名兇犯的鞋印
Boot prints from the two assailants.
還有朱莉·馬斯特的高跟鞋鞋印
And Julie Masters's heels.
那是什么
What do we got?
看來我們的證人做出了一番抵抗
Looks like our witness was a fighter.
-我認為她傷到了其中一位  -干得好
- I think she hurt one of them. - Good for her.
九毫米口徑  三個彈殼
Nine mil. Three casings.
這是她的指紋
This is her print.
這么說她燒傷了槍手
So she burns the shooter
從窗戶跳了出去
and dives through the window.
我希望她還活著  我很想見見她
I really hope she's alive, 'cause I want to meet her.
是啊  看起來她的割傷很嚴重
Yeah. Looks like she cut herself pretty good.
-阿成  -史蒂夫
- Chin. - Hey, Steve.
我在警車這
I'm back by the blue and whites.
你得來看看
You need to see this.
什么情況
What you got?
你殺死了聯邦執法官和兩名警官
You kill a federal marshal and two officers,
唯一的問題是你想怎么死
the only question is how are you going to get put down?
這么說她一個人在外面
So she's out there somewhere, alone.
還被職業殺手追殺
And being hunted by professional assassins.
我們得趕在他們前面找到她
So we have to find her before they do,
還要確保她今天能出庭作證
and make sure she testifies today.
我們從哪找起
Where do we start?
好了  水  即食食物
All right. Water. MREs.
全球定位儀  衛星電話
GPS. Sat phones. Okay?
在這個地帶  想要找到他們所需的東西
Everything we need to track them in this terrain.
帶著搜查犬的火奴魯魯警警察在路上
HPD is en route with search dogs.
剛剛收到的消息  十分鐘之內
Hey. Just got word that air support's lifting off
空中支援將從火奴魯魯起飛
from Honolulu in ten minutes.
他們在這找不到直升機可以降落的地方
They can't find a place to land a chopper around here.
最近的停機坪離這里有三英里
Nearest LZ is three miles away.
沒關系
That's fine.
在這么茂密的樹林中
In this dense foliage and canopy,
找到她最好的辦法還是跟蹤足跡
our best shot at finding her is tracking, anyway.
-阿成  確認一下這些都是可用的  -好的
- Chin, make sure these are good to go. - Copy that.
-科諾  -說
- Kono? - Yeah?
聯系美國司法部  好嗎
Contact the U.S. Attorney, okay?
找到關于這個被告艾倫·布萊納的一切資料
Find out everything you can about this defendant Aaron Brenner.
然后和毒品管制局核實一下
Then check with the DEA.
我要知道巴哈販毒集團
I want to know who the Baja Cartel
通過誰執行暗殺
contracts its hits through.
我們得知道對手是誰
We need to know what we're up against out there.
好的  沒問題
All right. You got it.
伙計們  過來
Guys, come on in.
我們需要你們封鎖犯罪現場
We need you guys to lock down the crime scene
以防證人或是兇手跑回來  好嗎
in case the witness or the killers double back. Okay?
如果證人回來了
The witness comes back,
直接護送她去法院
you get her straight to the courthouse.
兇手要是回來了
The shooters come back,
干掉他們
you put them down,
確保他們被干掉了
and you make sure they stay down.
格蕾絲
Grace?
爸爸
Daddy!
上來
Come here.
我看到他的時候  他已經打開了車門
By the time I saw him, he'd had opened the door.
他們拿著槍
They had guns.
我都聽見了
I heard everything.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
愛德華茲太太
Mrs. Edwards?
我們找到了你的奔馳車
We've recovered your Mercedes.
你的提包完好無損
Your purse is intact,
現金和信用卡都在里面
money and credit cards all there.
沒有東西被偷走
Nothing seems to be stolen.
我松了一口氣  謝謝
Well, that's a relief. Thank you.
奔馳  你在開斯坦的車嗎
Mercedes? You were driving Stan's car?
是啊  他在泰國談生意
Yeah. He's in Thailand on business.
有時候我們換車開
Sometimes we switch cars.
我跟你談談
Let me talk to you for a second.
我到那邊去和媽媽談話  好嗎
I'm gonna be right there talking to your mom, okay?
你能看見我們
You can see us.
我要你獲取這個家伙的一切信息
I want you to get all this guy's information,
看看他都干了什么  好嗎
see what he's doing, okay?
這邊
Come here.
如果他們把格蕾絲劫走怎么辦
What if they had taken Grace?
他們沒有  你干得很好  保護了她
They didn't. You did a good job and you protected her, okay?
這是怎么回事
What's going on?
好吧
Okay, um...
持槍劫車是要判十年的  知道嗎
armed carjacking is a ten-year sentence.Okay?
蕾切爾  任何打算持槍劫車的人
Rachel, anybody willing to do that,
都甘愿冒這個險
willing to take that risk,
他們不會只是在一個小時后棄車的
they're not gonna just dump the car an hour later.
劫車是為了錢
Okay? You jack a car for money.
你那上萬美元的奔馳車
Your hundred thousand dollar Mercedes,
被海運到中國
it gets put on a boat to China,
某人就能迅速掙到2萬美元
and somebody gets a fast $20,000.
他們不會還車  他們不會留下你的錢包
They don't return the car, they don't leave your purse,
他們也不會留下你的現金
they don't leave your cash.
所以為什么
So why?
我是說  如果動機和錢財無關
I mean, there's no profit motive.
為什么有人會這么做
Why would someone do this?
我不知道  你什么意思
Mm, I don't know. What are you saying?
斯坦在家的表現
Anything at all strange
-有什么異常嗎  任何...  -沒有
- going on with Stan at home? - Any... No.
-你確定  -確定
- You sure? - Yes.
好吧  因為我覺得極有可能
Okay, 'cause I think that there's a very high possibility
這是有人在傳遞訊息
that someone is sending a message,
威脅  告訴斯坦說他們能傷害到你
a threat, telling Stan that they can get to you
也能傷害到格蕾絲
and they can get to Grace.
斯坦是我的丈夫  是格蕾絲的繼父
Stan is my husband, he's Grace's stepfather,
他是個正經生意人
and... he is a businessman.
他絕對不會卷入任何非法的事情里去
He's not involved in anything illegal.
我想帶格蕾絲回家
I would like to take Grace home.
我開車送你們
Okay, I'll drive you.
火奴魯魯  聯邦法院
羅伯茨檢察官
Prosecuting Attorney Roberts.
卡拉克瓦警官  我收到了你的信息
Officer Kalakaua, I got your message.
我能為你做什么
How can I help you?
我需要一份
I'm gonna need a list of the
知道今天要移交證人的人員名單
people who knew about the witness transfer today.
沒幾個人  我的手下和幾位高級緝毒署探員
It's a short list-- my people and a few high-level DEA agents.
我會讓我辦公室的人馬上給你們發過去
I'll have my office send it over to you right away.
我也需要能夠進入你電腦系統的
Okay, I'm also gonna need full access
-全權授權  -沒問題
- to your computer system.  - Of course.
無論你要什么  只管開口
I'll get you anything you need.
已經有三個人死亡了  你怎么知道朱莉還活著
You've got three dead. How do you know Julie's still alive?
我們不知道  但是她九死一生
We don't, but she got out of the house
沖出了那棟房子  如果她在外面的某處
against all odds, and if she's out there,
我們就會找到她
we'll find her.
這就是那三個
This is what happened to the last three people
原定要指控販毒集團的證人的下場
who were scheduled to testify against the cartel.
像朱莉·馬斯特這樣的人
How does someone like Julie Masters
是怎么和巴哈販毒集團扯上關系的
get involved with the Baja Cartel?
她是火奴魯魯一家進口公司的會計
She was an accountant at an import company in Honolulu.
她不知道那家公司
She didn't know it was a front
只是艾倫·布萊納毒品生意的幌子
for Aaron Brenner's drug operation.
某夜  一個碼頭工人正在給一艘貨柜船裝箱
One night a dockworker is loading crates into a container ship,
-發現了他們真正運輸的東西  -海洛因
- discovers what they're really shipping. - Cocaine.
對
Exactly.
艾倫·布萊納冷血地殺害了那個人
Aaron Brenner executed the man in cold blood,
朱莉目擊了這場謀殺
and Julie witnessed the murder.
他試圖殺害她  但她跑了
He tried to kill her; she ran.
從此她就開始了逃亡生涯
She's been running ever since.
如果今天下午5點朱莉到不了法院
If Julie's not in that courtroom by 5:00 p.m. today,
布萊納將會無罪釋放
Brenner's a free man.
你怎么知道他們從這條路走了
How do you know they went this way?
在這樣的地域追蹤他人  關鍵在于一件事
Tracking humans in terrain like this is about one thing--
看看有什么非自然的現象
seeing what's out of context in nature
然后了解其成因
and knowing what caused it.
就好像那塊被扳倒的石板
Like that flat overturned rock back up there.
那需要一個體重200磅的人
It would've taken a 200-pound man
下坡時才會弄倒
running downhill to do that.
那石板也表明了
That rock also indicated
他們是一個小時前到達的那里
they're about an hour ahead of us.
真的  一塊石板就能告訴你這么多
Really? The rock told you that?
-看到地上的那葉子了嗎  -看到
- See that leaf on the ground? - Yeah.
還綠著呢
It's still green.
剛剛被折下來的  掩護我
It was just broken off-- cover me.
走向我
Walk towards me.
我不會鳴槍示警
I will not fire a warning shot.
朱莉
Julie.
朱莉  放下武器好嗎
Julie, put down the weapon, okay?
放下武器  走向我
Put down the weapon and walk
我們是警察
towards me-- we're cops.
之前那倆也是
So were the last two.
可能會有一點點疼
This might sting.
絕不能讓艾倫·布萊納逍遙法外
There's no way Aaron Brenner's going to get away with this.
你把我帶去法院  我會作證的
You get me to that courtroom, and I'll testify.
阿成會帶你過去
Chin will get you there.
聽著  除非必要  否則不要用槍  好嗎
Listen, don't use your gun unless you have to, okay?
你絕對不希望引起注意
You don't want to draw attention to yourself.
朱莉  把你的鞋子給我
Julie, let me have your shoes.
脫下來  把鞋子給我
Take 'em off, give me your shoes.
阿成  沿著山脊線走  直接去馬凱
Chin... follow the ridgeline, okay, head to Makai.
山脊線會帶你重回大道
It'll lead you back to the road
而那會讓你處于有利位置能夠看清
and it'll give me a better vantage point
-是不是有人追上你們  -收到
- on the guys when they pick up your trail. - Copy.
你為什么不和我們一起走
Why aren't you coming with us?
我要去撂倒那兩個
I'm gonna hunt down the guys
試圖傷害你的人
that have been trying to hurt you.
有些人  生來就不知道害怕
Some guys... they're just born without a fear gene.
艾倫·布萊納
Aaron Brenner.
來給我配偶探監的就是你吧
Oh, you must be my conjugal visit.
你下令謀殺兩名火奴魯魯警官
You ordered the murders of two HPD officers
-和一名聯邦執法官  -你能證明嗎
- and a federal marshal. - And you can prove that?
朱莉·馬斯特能  她很快就到
Julie Masters can, and she'll be here soon.
-我搭檔會確保她及時趕到  -離我客戶遠一點
- My partners will make sure of that. - Get away from my client.
我已經等不及想看
I can't wait to see the look in your eyes
當她走進法庭作證時你的表情了
when she walks into that courtroom and testifies.
如果她能作證的話
If she testifies.
警長  帶布萊納先生出去
Sheriffs, take Mr. Brenner out of here
然后讓他在等候區等待
and put him in the holding area now.
我會向法官投訴
I'm lodging a complaint against you
你騷擾我的客戶
for harassment with the judge.
有些人就是拼不對我的名字
You know, some people have trouble with my name,
所以我來幫幫你
so let me help you out.
我叫科諾·卡拉克瓦
It's Kono Kalakaua.
K-a-l-a-k-a-u-a
K-a-l-a-k-a-u-a.
-我想不是你把門開著沒關吧  -不是
- Don't suppose you left that door open. - No.
911報警電話  你有什么緊急情況要報警
911 operator. What is your emergency?
我是丹尼·威廉姆斯警探
This is Detective Danny Williams.
我的警徽號是7576
My badge number is 7576.
請派兩輛警車到庫里奧  薩默街4347號
I need two squad cars to 4347 Summer Street, Kuli'ou'ou--
可能有人正在盜竊
possible burglary in progress.
-收到  他們就在路上  -謝謝
- Roger that. They're on their way. -Thank you.
聽我說  我要你去街上開車兜一兜
Okay, listen to me. Want you to drive around the block.
我確認一切安全了就給你打電話  好嗎
I'll call you when it's safe, okay?
好
Okay.
你
You,
你要和你媽媽去兜兜風
you're gonna go for a little ride with your mom, okay?
我5分鐘就來
I'll be out in five minutes.
你還沒有說完"我愛你  丹諾"我就回來了
I'll be back faster than you can say, "I love you, Danno," okay?
跟車子的情況一樣
Just like the car, it seems
看上去貴重物品都在
like nothing of value was taken.
斯坦的辦公室看上去像被風暴襲擊了一樣
And Stan's office looks like a tornado hit it.
你還是進去  打包些你和格蕾絲的東西
So why don't you go inside, pack a bag for you and Grace?
-什么  這是...  -我希望在搞清楚
- What? Where...? - I want you to go
到底發生了什么之前
to a hotel for a couple of days until I figure out
你們能去酒店住幾天
what is going on here.
斯坦一個小時之內會到家
Stan will be home in an hour
我們會想出應對方法
and we'll figure out what we're going to do.
對于我女兒的安全
Okay, Stan does not get to make decisions
斯坦無權做決定
regarding the safety of my daughter,
所以說她可以和你一起去住希爾頓
so she can go to the Hilton with you
或者她可以過來和愛她的
or she can come on what is affectionately known
父親一起住
as a ride along with her father.
好嗎
Okay?
我去打包
I'll pack.
但我不想讓她看見房子里面的樣子
But I don't want her to see the house.
她現在已經夠驚恐了  我不希望她更害怕
It will only make her more scared than she already is.
蕾切爾
Rachel.
無論那里發生了什么  我告訴你
Whatever is going on here, I am telling you
斯坦肯定脫不了干系  好嗎
that Stan is in the middle of it. Okay?
丹尼  格蕾絲和蕾切爾還好嗎
Danny, are Grace and Rachel okay?
她們很安全  但我很不舒服
Yeah, they are safe, but I am sick.
我還余驚未消
I'm in the middle of a panic attack.
這次小意外讓我少活5年
Okay, this little incident just shaved five years off my life.
目擊證人如何了  你找到她了嗎
What's up with the witness? You find her yet?
找到了  但別擔心
Yeah, yeah, but don't worry about that.
你和家人待在一起
Okay, you stay with your family.
-別過來了  -好  我不去
- Don't come out here.  - Okay, I'm not.
實際上我正在去往機場的路上
I'm actually on my way to the airport.
你說什么  機場  怎么了  你要去哪
What are you talking about, airport? Why, you going someplace?
斯坦  斯坦回家了
Well, Stan... Stan comes home and, uh,
過去接他回家
go offer him a lift home.
丹尼  你在做什么
Danny, what are you doing?
我什么都沒做
I'm not doing anything.
聽著  好嗎
Listen, okay...
我也許看不見你  但我能聽見你的聲音
I may not be able to see you, okay, but I can hear you,
-而且你有那么一種語氣  -語氣  我才沒有
- and you have a tone. - Tone. I don't have a tone.
-我沒語氣  -你不是一直說我有個表情嗎
- I don't have a tone. - Okay, you say I have a face?
那你  我的朋友  有種語氣
You, my friend, you have a tone,
那種語氣說明"我要狠狠揍一個人"
okay, and it's a tone that says "I'm gonna hit somebody."
現在告訴我  發生什么了
Now, what's going on?
好吧  我覺得斯坦
Okay, I think that Stan--
事實上我知道斯坦和發生在
in fact I know that Stan has something to do
蕾切爾和格蕾絲身上的事有千絲萬縷的聯系
with what happened to Rachel and Grace.
好  除了你痛恨那男人之外
Okay. Is that based in anything
你有沒有其他證據
other than the fact that you hate the man?
是  有證據  好嗎
Yes. It is, okay?
他們偷的是他的車  他們劫的是他的車
They stole his car. They-They got his car.
而不是她的  好嗎
Not hers, okay?
而且他們一小時之內就還了車
And they returned it in an hour,
他們沒帶走任何東西
and they didn't take anything.
他們的房子被人強行闖入  翻得亂七八糟
All right, the house was broken into, ransacked,
就和那車一樣  他們什么都沒帶走
and just like the car, they took nothing.
好嗎  你聽著正常嗎
Okay? Does that sound normal to you?
我女兒
All right, my daughter...
我女兒在那房子里睡覺  好嗎
my daughter sleeps in that house, okay?
如果斯坦和這件事情有關系
And-and if Stan has anything to do with it,
我會"鼓勵"他  交代他知道的一切
I am going to encourage him to tell me what he knows.
好  聽我說好嗎
Okay, listen to me. All right?
我知道你很生氣  我能聽出來
I get that you're pissed, all right? I can hear that.
但是無論你做什么
But whatever you do,
別揍他  好嗎
do not touch him, okay?
別碰他一根汗毛
Do not touch him.
我知道  但是你得理解一下
Yeah, I understand, but you got to understand
我是位父親
that I am a father.
好嗎  而我們現在討論的是我的女兒
All right? And this is my daughter we're talking about.
對  但你還是一名帶槍警察  好嗎
Yeah. You're also a cop with a gun, okay?
當你兩個身份交錯時  事情會變得很混亂  丹尼
And when those worlds cross, it gets messy, Danny.
對  但不是我讓兩個身份交錯的
Yeah, well, I'm not the one who crossed them.
就別擔心我了  我應付得來
Just don't-don't worry about me. Please. I will handle it.
把目擊證人帶去法院  好嗎
Just get your witness to court, okay?
不不  喂喂  丹尼
No. No. Hey, hey. Hey, hey. Danny.
丹尼
Danny?
在第一次審判開始的時候我跑回了內陸
You must think I'm an awful person for running back to
你肯定覺得我是個很糟糕的人
the mainland when the first trial started.
我不知道有關你的任何事
I don't know anything about you.
我不知道你為什么走
I have no idea why you left,
但我相信你一定有自己的原因
but I'm sure you have your reasons.
是因為我的妹妹
It's my sister.
她比我小5歲
She's five years younger than me.
她是我最好的朋友
She's my best friend.
好  這么說你想見你妹妹
All right. So you wanted to see your sister
而且你知道一旦你作證
and you knew if you testified,
他們就會讓你加入證人保護計劃  我明白
they'd put you in witness protection? I get it.
當他們第一次用頻譜為麗莎做出診斷
When they first diagnosed Lisa on the spectrum,
我太小  根本不清楚那意味著什么
I was too young to know what it all meant.
她有自閉癥嗎
She has autism?
一直是我媽媽照顧她
My mom's been taking care of her,
但照顧她變得越來越困難
but it's getting too hard for her.
我來到這里完成學業
I came here to finish school
之后我就可以照顧她了
and then I was supposed to take care of her.
那你為什么回來
Why would you come back?
我本以為麗莎不懂這些事
I didn't think Lisa understood any of this.
然后有天晚上  很晚了  都過11點了
And then one night, it was late-- it was after 11:00,
通常情況下她9點就上床睡覺了
and she usually goes to bed at 9:00--
她就那么看著我
she just looked at me,
她說我必須得回夏威夷
and she said that I had to go back to Hawaii
確保壞人不會再傷害別人了
and make sure that the bad man didn't hurt anyone else.
你是個勇敢的女人
You're a brave woman.
又死了三個人
Three more people are dead,
我可能永遠都見不到我妹妹了
and I may never see my sister.
我必須要回到法庭上去
I have to get back to that courthouse.
好  走
All right, let's go.
好的
Okay.
我們走了一半多了
We're more than halfway now.
你表現的很棒
You're doing great.
趴下
Get down!
堅持住
Hold on.
Hold on. Okay.
我數到三  拉你上來
I'm going to pull you up on three.
好嗎
Okay?
一  二  三
One, two, three.
繼續往前走
Keep going straight ahead.
我一會兒追上你
I'll be right behind you.
別怕  別怕  是我
It's okay. It's okay. It's me.
我把他引向了另一個方向
Now, I've pointed him in another direction,
但是他一會兒就會發現
but he's going to figure it out soon enough.
我們繼續走  好嗎
We've just got to keep moving, okay?
往前走  走吧
Straight ahead. Let's go.
你醒了
You're up.
很好
Good.
我要問你幾個問題
I wanted to ask you a couple questions.
你們一共有幾個人被派到夏威夷
How many of you were sent to Hawaii?
不是吧  這個時候你讓我問第二遍
Seriously? You going to make me ask you twice right now?
一共三個人
Three of us were sent here.
你們從哪飛過來的
Where did you fly in from?
圣何塞
San Jose.
哥斯達黎加
Costa Rica.
招供多簡單啊  早說不就完了嗎
See how easy that was?
求你別殺我
Please.
我都招了
I told you what you want to know.
我不會折磨你的  好嗎
I'm not going to torture you, okay?
我要救你
I'm going to save your life.
剛剛的撞擊導致你氣胸
You have a collapsed lung.
我要在你胸腔打個洞
I need to cut a hole in your chest
讓你的肺重新鼓起來
and reinflate your lung,
否則你會沒命的  好嗎
or you're going to die. All right?
你最好咬著它
You may want to chew on that.
別出聲
Don't make any noise.
科諾
Kono.
有成浩的消息嗎
Did you hear from Chin Ho?
沒有
No.
怎么了  你們倆不是在一起嗎
Why? You don't have eyes on him?
我們分頭行動  他護送證人
No. We split up, but he has the witness.
別擔心  他沒事  你有什么發現
Don't worry, he'll be fine. What do you got?
我還是查不出殺手團伙的身份  你那邊呢
I still have no ID on the hit squad. Any luck on your end?
我制服了一名襲擊者
Yeah. I disabled one of the attackers.
他承認他們一伙是昨天
He confessed to being part of the team
從哥斯達黎加飛來的
that flew in from Costa Rica yesterday.
我馬上檢查哥斯達黎加方向的航班記錄
Okay. I'm checking flight manifests from Costa Rica.
他說有三名暗殺者  知道嗎
He said there were three assassins, okay?
也就是說  我們要找四個人
Which means we're looking for four people--
三名槍手和一名清道夫
three shooters and a cleaner.
清道夫  清道夫是什么意思
Cleaner? What's a cleaner?
另一位刺殺者  我的海豹突擊隊
It's another assassin. My SEAL team used
曾經打擊過這種殺手團伙  槍手們
to hunt squads like this. The shooters don't know
對清道夫的身份一無所知
the identity of the cleaner,
所以如果他們被俘  還有一位槍手
so if they get captured, there's still another shooter
可以完成任務
in place to pull the trigger.
昨天有一班
All right. There was one flight in
從哥斯達黎加到火奴魯魯的飛機
from Costa Rica to Honolulu yesterday.
并且
And...
三名乘客現金付款
three of the passengers paid in cash.
能在監控錄像上找到他們嗎
Okay, can you pull them up on the security cam?
找到了
I got them.
知道嗎
You know what?
我沒發現有誰像清道夫
I'm not seeing the fourth guy who could be the cleaner.
進行面部識別  檢查所有記錄
Run facial recognition. Go through the records.
留意任何能幫我們找到清道夫的線索
Look for any clues that might lead to the cleaner.
同時  讓急救醫療中心派一架救傷直升機
In the meantime, have EMS send a medevac.
告訴他們著陸之后步行
Tell them to insert and then proceed on foot
到經緯坐標27.97  156.95的位置
to coordinates 27.97 -156.95.
收到
Will do.
你好
Hey, there.
愛德華茲
去希爾頓夏威夷度假村713房間  謝謝
Hilton Hawaiian Village, room 713. Thanks.
謝天謝地你和格蕾絲安然無恙
Just thank God you and Grace are okay, baby.
是的
Yeah.
聽著  我在路上  馬上就到
All right, listen. I'm on the way. I'll be there soon.
丹尼
Danny?
是我  我來找你談談
Yeah. I got to talk to you.
我可沒有征求你的意見  過來  過來
I'm not asking you. Come on. Come on.
我跟你說  斯坦
You know, Stan,
有了女兒之后  我知道有些事
when I had a daughter, I knew that there were certain things
不得不去面對
I was going to have to deal with.
收發短信  要給她買很多衣服
Texting. An obscene clothing budget.
不管我選擇什么樣的套餐
A stroke-inducing cell phone bill,
花費都很高的手機話費賬單
regardless of the plan that I chose,
但我告訴你
but I'll tell you,
有一件事  我可沒想到會發生
there is one thing that did not make the list. Okay.
那就是被人劫車
Carjacking.
我從沒想過我那八歲的
Carjacking did not make the list of things that I thought that
寶貝女兒會遭人劫車
I would encounter with my eight-year-old daughter.
所以我只問你這一次
So I am going to ask you one time.
你惹了什么麻煩
What kind of trouble are you in?
和我沒關系  丹諾
This has nothing to do with me, Danny.
我和你一樣震驚
I'm as shocked as you are.
住口
Shut up.
住口  好嗎
Shut up. Okay?
我想讓你知道
I want you to know something.
要是以前  我會把車停下  把你揍得
Normally, I would just pull over and give you the worst beating
你母親都認不出來  直到你說實話
you ever had in your entire life until you told me the truth,
但我正在克制  克制
but I am working, I am working
情緒失控問題
on my anger management issues,
我正學著如何解決沖突  你懂嗎
and I am learning conflict resolution, you understand?
而且我發現了端倪  我發現
And I recognize something. I recognize,
盡管你試圖掩蓋
although you are trying to hide it,
你內心卻相當害怕  你也應該害怕
you are very scared right now, as you should be,
但證據不足  我姑且
but I am going to give you
相信你說的都是真的  但我要提醒你
the benefit of the doubt and I am going to remind you
正是因為你  有人拿槍接近了我女兒
that because of you, people put guns near my daughter.
為了批準我的新地產
I went to the housing commissioner,
我找過房產委員
Bruce Hoffman,
布魯斯·霍夫曼
for permits for my new property.
那家伙給我一份"菜單"
Guy hands me a menu
好像在紐約西普里尼酒店一樣
like we're at Cipriani's in New York.
明碼標價
Everything's got a price.
每次我同意一個數額
Every time I agreed to a number,
他都不知足得抬高要價
he jacked it up to a higher one.
所以我把談話錄了下來  說要起訴他
So I taped the conversation, told him I'd have him indicted.
這才是他們要找的  那卷磁帶
So that's what they're looking for. The tapes?
丹尼  對天發誓  我永遠不會
Danny, I swear to God, I never...
為什么不直接找我
Why didn't you just come to me?
-你在說笑嗎  -沒有
- Are you kidding? - No, I'm not.
聽著
Look,
我和蕾切爾最近關系有點僵
things haven't been great with Rachel and me lately.
但我愛她  丹尼  也愛格蕾絲
But I love her, Danny, and I love Grace.
這項交易會使我們從中受益
This deal could make a lot of things right for us.
好吧  聽著
Okay. Uh, listen.
格蕾絲和蕾切爾會住在希爾頓酒店...
Grace and Rachel are going to be staying at the Hilton...
你真的認為...
You really think...
他們劫了你的車
Hey. They jacked your car.
闖入了你的房子
They broke into your house.
那是我女兒
That is my daughter.
是的  斯坦  我就是這么認為
So, yes, Stan, I think.
給你  不用找了
Here you go. Keep the rest.
非常感謝
Thanks a lot.
你是不是房產委員
Aren't you the housing commissioner, right?
我是布魯斯·霍夫曼
Bruce Hoffman.
你們都出去  來
I need this room. Come on.
快快快  出去
Come on, come on. Come on, come on.
走  出去
Go ahead. Come on, out, out.
我是丹尼·威廉姆斯警探
I'm Detective Danny Williams.
你為了警告斯坦·愛德華茲
I am also the father of that little girl
今天早上劫持了一輛奔馳
that was in the Mercedes that you had carjacked this morning,
我的女兒就坐在上面
sending a message to Stan Edwards.
磁帶現在在我這  不在他手上
I have the tapes now. He doesn't have them anymore.
我來問問你
I'm going to ask you a question.
如果磁帶曝光了會發生什么
What do you think would happen if those tapes got out? Huh?
聽著  我不知道
Look, look. I... I don't know anything
你在說什么
about what you're talking about,
威廉姆斯...
Detective...
威廉姆斯
Williams.
你可以把我的警號從額頭上抄下來
You can get my badge number off your forehead.
磁帶在我手上  我會揭發你
I have those tapes, and will expose you,
如果你再敢
and if you ever, ever
讓人拿槍接近我女兒
put a gun in the same zip code as my daughter,
對天發誓  我會殺了你的
I swear to God, I will kill you.
懂了嗎
You understand?
-懂了  -是嗎
- Yeah. - Yeah?
-是的  -很好
- Yes. - Good.
跟緊點
Stay close.
好的
Okay.
該死
Damn it.
稍等
Hold on.
你不能打電話叫一架直升機嗎
Can't you just call for a helicopter?
我也想啊  但我的手機和槍一起掉下懸崖了
I would. But my phone went down the cliff with my gun.
-只剩一小時了  -騎摩托能趕上
- We've only got an hour left. - This bike'll get us there.
-他是以前的那伙人嗎  -不是
- Is he one of them? - No.
蹲下
Stay down.
阿成  是他
Chin, it's him.
另一個家伙
It's the other guy.
他繞過來了
He's coming around.
別動  別動
Don't move. Don't move.
蹲下
Get down.
上車
Get on the bike!
進去
Get in.
我是海軍少校史蒂夫·麥格瑞特
This is Lieutenant Commander Steve McGarrett.
證人朱莉·馬斯特受到保護
The witness, Julie Masters, is secure,
我們正要把她帶來
and we're bringing her in.
我要求法院周圍部署武裝守衛
All right, I want an armed perimeter guarding the courthouse.
還有一位潛在暗殺者
There's still a potential assassin
沒有被逮捕
who has not been apprehended.
我們乘卡車前往目的地
We're coming in by truck.
相信我  很容易認出我們的卡車
You'll know which truck, trust me.
我車里有備用的鞋和衣服
Uh, I have an extra pair of shoes and a sweater in my car.
我們得走了
We got to go.
謝謝你
Thank you.
為我做的一切
For everything.
不必再逃亡了
No more running.
去吧
Go.
看來證人最后還是現身了
I see that you've finally produced your witness.
她隨時可以作證
She's ready to testify.
我的委托人想跟你們庭外和解
My client would like to talk about a deal.
他認罪并供出毒品供應商的名字
He pleads guilty and gives up the names
和殺害兩名警察和一名聯邦執法官
of his suppliers and his coconspirators
的同謀名單
in the murders of the two cops and the federal marshal
作為交換  他免于死刑  改判終身監禁
in exchange for life in prison with no death penalty.
他會死在監獄  而不是被處死
He dies in prison instead of being executed,
作為交換
and in exchange,
我們還能多捉住十個艾倫·布萊納這樣的壞人  朱莉
we get to put ten more Aaron Brenners away for life, Julie.
你的合作律師呢  協議上他也必須簽名
Where's your co-counsel? He has to sign off on this.
他在會議室等著呢
He's waiting in the conference room.
科諾
Hey, Kono.
清道夫是布萊納的合作律師
Hey, the cleaner is Brenner's co-counsel.
金發  一米七
She's a blonde woman, five, seven,
她現在就在法院里
and she's in the courthouse right now.
他在哪
Where is he?
馬上就來
He'll be right in.
雖然還有很多事情我可以教你
You know, there might be a few other things I could teach you,
但是痛扁對手這項  你已經很嫻熟了
but I think you've got the whole ass-kicking thing down.
一切都好嗎
Is everything all right?
現在好了  多虧丹尼
Yeah, it is now, thanks to Danny.
是的  只是一場  誤會
Yeah, it was just a... misunderstanding.
斯坦不過是被卷入其中
Stan just got caught in the middle of it.
錯不在他  現在都解決了
You know, it wasn't his fault. It's over now.
再次感謝  丹尼
Thanks again, Danny. All right.
你
You.
-過兩天再見  好嗎  -好  我愛你  丹諾
- I'll see you later, okay? - Okay. I love you, Danno.
我也愛你
I love you, too.
走吧  孩子
Come on, kiddo.
再次感謝
Thanks again.
法官閣下  控方傳喚朱莉·馬斯特出庭作證
Your Honor, the prosecution calls Julie Masters.
你發誓你說的一切
Do you swear to tell the truth,
句句屬實  無半句虛假嗎
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth?
我發誓
I do.